-Today's the day.
-What day?
You don't remember?
Eden Academy will announce
the results of the entrance exam.
The results should be posted
at 12:00 p.m. today.
It's natural to be nervous.
My bracelet broke. Why today of all days?
It's just a coincidence.
Loid, look at that.
Come on, Yor.
Black cats are nothing but superstitions.
You're right.
-Father.
-What is it?
Anya stepped on poop.
Eden Academy's entrance exam results?
Oh, that thing
that agent Twilight is working on?
Director, peaceful relations
between East and West
depend on Operation Strix,
so please take this
a little more seriously.
You've never been acquainted
with Twilight, have you?
No, I have not.
He's known as the number one spy
in Westalis.
So don't worry.
You'll soon get a message that says
"the cherry blossoms have bloomed."
What does that mean?
It's a code used in the East.
It means "passed the exam."
It's not there.
ORIGINAL WORK BY TATSUYA ENDO
SERIALIZED ON SHUEISHA'S SHONEN JUMP PLUS
PASS OR FAIL?
We failed.
Let's go home.
I'll make some tea.
I'm sorry.
It's all because Anya stepped on poop.
Wait a moment, Forger family.
Mr. Henderson.
-What is this?
-Look at the top of the list.
Anya Forger.
Those are additional successful applicants
on the waiting list. It's confidential.
A waiting list?
Yes, Anya Forger scored first place
on the waiting list
according to her overall scores.
If one of the successful applicants
declines their place,
Anya will immediately fill that spot.
But why…
even after what we did.
Do you know what creature is responsible
for killing the most humans?
It's the mosquito.
That's right. You saved Mr. Swan
from that dangerous creature.
That gave you lots of additional points.
That's crazy.
Have confidence, Forger.
Your family deserves to be in our academy.
If even one vacant position opens up,
Anya will be accepted?
That's right.
But what if no one declines?
About that…
Thorn Princess! Why are you here?
You must be Secretary Scapegoat.
Will you allow me to take your life?
Stop it! Help!
I have a son who's about to turn six!
He's finally entering Eden Academy
next month!
He won't be able to go to school if I die!
I'm sorry, but that's exactly
what I'm after.
In order for Anya to fill
that vacant spot…
please die!
No! Yor, it's not right
to kill innocent people!
Yor?
It's nothing.
I'm sorry, Mr. Scapegoat.
Well, don't worry.
Every year there's always a few people
who decline their place.
Keep that in mind,
and make sure you're prepared.
Thank you.
Although I may be fired as a teacher
by the time school begins.
What?
I punched and knocked out that pig.
Between that fool and this teacher,
I don't know who will be more
useful to this mission
but there are countless ways to
kill that fool if he gets in the way.
Please let me know if we can be of help.
I appreciate the offer, elegant boy.
Go home and wait for the acceptance call.
THREE DAYS LATER
Anya is accepted
-Anya is accepted
-What is she doing?
She's performing a prayer ritual so that
she can get accepted.
Is that right?
Hello, Forger residence.
Yes…
Goodbye.
She got accepted!
Father, Anya is accepted!
-You did well, Anya!
-Hooray!
Congratulations! I'm so happy!
Thank you so much, Yor.
Hey, I heard you were accepted.
It's time for a celebration.
-You found out already?
-Don't underestimate the informant.
Hi, Mrs. Forger. Nice to meet you.
I'm Franky, Loid's friend.
-Nice to meet you.
-It's Scruffy.
It's time to party! I brought alcohol,
and ordered some food too.
You didn't even ask me first.
It's all thanks to me,
as I stole the answer sheet.
You idiot! They can hear you.
What? What did you say?
Hey, are you really drinking?
Why are you sober?
Leave me alone.
Anya, you're in luck.
Your dad says he'll buy you
whatever you want as a reward.
Stop making up promises.
Anya doesn't want anything,
but wants to do something instead.
What is it?
I'll grant it if it's within my means.
Help me, Bondman!
Good morning, Bondman.
Your mission this time
is to rescue Princess Honey who has been
imprisoned by the League of Evil,
and to restore her castle.
Wait for me, Princess Honey!
The one who infiltrated the castle
is the kingdom's number one spy.
Bondman!
He defeated all the enemies,
and finally made it to Princess Honey.
I'm here to rescue you, Princess Honey.
Bondman!
Peace was restored in the castle
and they lived happily ever after.
Anya wants to do this.
You want to do that? What do you mean?
-Rescue roleplay at a castle!
-Impossible. Declined.
How mean. You're the devil.
If you can't do this for me,
I won't go to school.
Stop speaking for her.
Isn't that Newston Castle?
It was recently renovated into
an amusement park themed around this show.
The attractions are based on scenes
from the show, and you can rent it out.
Hey Loid, that area isn't
backed by the government
so it'll be okay to have some fun.
But…
You worked so hard to pass the exam,
didn't you?
You won't be able to go on
without a congratulatory gift, right?
Fine.
Okay! Strike while the iron is hot!
Leave the castle reservation up to me.
Find a way for us to get there.
You're planning on going today?
And you want me to help prepare?
Of course. It's for your daughter.
A message from Twilight.
Code GO-005.
He did it.
The cherry blossoms have bloomed.
-Another message from Twilight.
-What is it?
What should we do?
He's known as the number one spy
in Westalis.
-Make the arrangements right away!
-Roger.
Rheineck district. To Falcon.
Important case from Twilight.
Falcon speaking.
Roger to the important case from Twilight.
1830. Rheineck district.
In the downstream region of Nhine River.
They're so quick to respond.
You can even do this at the castle.
Anya will think of a quiz!
Good idea.
It's just as I expected of you!
It's Anya's first time on an airplane.
I'm so excited.
You're all set.
-Does Anya look cool?
-You're very cool.
Loid.
How did you get this light aircraft?
You're so amazing.
Oh, I'm borrowing it from my co-worker.
Thank you for always being so kind
to my husband.
Does everyone have their seatbelts on?
We're going to take off.
Let's go!
Anya is so excited!
Hooray!
Wow, it's so beautiful.
It looks like a jewelry box.
Father is amazing.
Hey, we can see it now!
Wow!
-The castle is so cool!
-Hey, quiet down.
We're about to land,
so stay in your seats.
It's the castle!
Franky, why are you running with her?
I'm glad it worked out.
What's wrong?
-This isn't what I expected.
-What do you mean?
A castle isn't a castle without enemies
and servants.
Anya is deflated.
I don't think I can go to school.
You're right.
You won't be able to go to school, right?
Daddy has to do something, right?
A message from Twilight.
He's requesting personnel.
Whomever we can spare.
It's time to put WISE to the test.
A notice to all agents in Ostania.
Participate in the emergency operation
at Newston Castle.
This is a top priority mission
in connection with Operation Strix.
This mission is a rank above SS.
I repeat. This is a top priority mission
in connection with Operation Strix.
This mission is a rank above SS.
That's Twilight in the flesh.
I want his autograph.
This organization is very capable.
Come up with a plan,
and leave the explaining up to me.
Fine.
Thank you for gathering here today
for my daughter.
-It's morse code.
-Listen. Carefully.
It's an order from Twilight!
I'd like you to roleplay as the enemy
fighting against the spy…
THIS MISSION IS IN CONNECTION
WITH OPERATION STRIX
SO NO NEED FOR FURTHER INQUIRY.
who's trying to save the princess.
I have no idea what's going on…
But it's Twilight. There must be
a purpose behind this strategy.
Please accept this favor
on behalf of my daughter.
I will start casting the roles.
Today's main character is…
Princess Anya!
The spy who will save Anya is
Loidman.
The head of the evil organization is
Count Scruffy.
Mother will be… she'll just be something.
No way.
All of you will play the capable minions
working under Count Scruffy!
I want you all
to come up with amazing ways
to prevent Loidman
from succeeding his mission.
Wait…
This mission is a rank above SS.
We must sacrifice everything
to succeed in this mission.
It's against Twilight,
so it's the real deal!
This day has finally come.
The tactics and strategies you use
to stop Loidman
will be up to you.
The success
of this operation lies in your hands.
That's not an exaggeration.
This is getting out of hand.
My minions! This is for Princess Anya!
Be sure to make Loidman suffer!
Are you ready?
-Get in position!
-Roger!
I've kidnapped Princess Anya!
If you want her back, come and get me!
Help me, Loidman.
What? It started already?
Hey!
Loidman! You will have to face
many difficult challenges
in order to save the princess.
First, we're going to present you with
a quiz created by our princess.
If you can't answer,
you'll have to put that on.
-This is…
-That's right!
-It's Bondman's costume!
-How exciting.
Here's the question.
What does Princess Anya
like about Bondman?
His face?
Wrong. I like him because he carries
a silent gun.
What? Really?
What? You didn't even know that
and you call yourself a father?
Next!
What is Anya's favorite food?
-Peanuts!
-Correct!
That was too easy.
This is the last question. If you can't
answer this, change into that costume!
Yeah, if I can't answer it.
Here's the question.
What does Anya want the most right now?
Something she wants right now?
Five, four, three…
I didn't know there was a time limit!
I never said there wouldn't be one either.
Calm down. What does Anya want?
Bondman's spy goods.
Princess Anya, what's the answer?
Right now…
Anya is thirsty so she wants water!
Loidman was incorrect!
How was I supposed to know that?
That was too bad, Loidman.
You have to keep your promise!
Anya really wants to see it
I want to see the perfect Loidman
Loidman!
Now onto the next stage!
Wait!
Loidman!
Come up here if you want to save
Princess Anya.
He's so cool!
He's so strong.
Loidman is so cool!
The game has only begun.
Oh no, help me.
What a hassle.
Loidman, I'm over here.
Anya is right here.
This isn't going anywhere.
How cool!
Do your best, minions! Don't give in!
Loid! Get hit!
What have you done?
Don't think you can get to me that easily!
Bye.
Help me, Loidman.
Loidman, you're amazing!
You came a long way, Loidman!
I'm not handing over the Princess.
Help me, Loidman.
I have to continue this embarrassing
roleplay in front of these agents?
But… it's for my mission.
Give me back the princess.
I never thought I'd get to see
Twilight acting out a role!
You idiot. Did you think I'd hand her over
that easily?
Come on out!
It's the world's deadliest witch,
Yorticia. Tear that man into pieces!
There's a witch?
I can't follow along with this plot.
What? No way…
I will not allow anyone
to take Anya!
Yor! Calm down.
Why is she physically attacking me
when she's a witch?
She's strong. She's going to get me.
Yor. Are you okay?
Anya…
You sure came a long way, Loidman!
But you can't defeat me that easily--
How exciting.
I'm here to rescue you, Princess Anya.
Father!
What? My character is your father?
It's shiny and bright!
Congratulations, Anya!
Congratulations… Anya.
What is this?
There's been lots of excitement
ever since I left the orphanage.
It's all thanks to Father.
I'm glad to hear that.
Anya will work hard at school.
Okay.
Anyways…
congratulations on your acceptance.
It's the invoice from Twilight.
Are you sure the numbers are right?
It's correct.
-But…
-It's correct!
REPORT NO. 006 - OPERATION STRIX
PHASE 1: ENSURE TO PASS THE ENTRANCE EXAM
THE FRIENDSHIP SCHEME
Subtitle translation by: Lili Morita